<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<RelativeLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    android:id="@+id/termsMainrel"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:background="@drawable/background_img" >

    <RelativeLayout
        android:id="@+id/terms_header_rellayout"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:background="#474C52" >

        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/terms_txt_top"
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"
            android:layout_centerVertical="true"
            android:padding="10dp"
            android:text="Terms and Conditions"
            android:textColor="#ffffff"
            android:textSize="@dimen/title_text"
            android:textStyle="bold" />
    </RelativeLayout>

    <ScrollView
        android:id="@+id/scrollView"
        android:layout_width="fill_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_above="@+id/terms_lnr_acceptBtns"
        android:layout_below="@id/terms_header_rellayout"
        android:layout_marginBottom="10dp" >

        <LinearLayout
            android:id="@+id/linearScroll"
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:orientation="vertical"
            android:padding="10dp" >

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/txt_instruction1"
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_marginTop="10dp"
                android:text="The following are terms of a legal agreement between you and That\'s It on its behalf and on behalf of its subsidiaries and affiliates (That\'s It). By accessing, browsing and/or using this site, you acknowledge that you have read, understood and agree to abide by and comply with all terms, conditions and notices contained in or referenced by these Terms and Conditions of Use. You further agree to be governed by any additional terms and conditions that may apply to you arising out your accessing, browsing and/or using of this site, whether contained on this site or in a separate agreement with That\'s It. In the event of any conflict between these Terms and Conditions of Use and such additional terms and conditions, such additional terms and conditions shall govern to the extent of the conflict. That\'s It reserves the right, in its discretion, to update or revise these Terms and Conditions of Use and to post such updated or revised Terms and Conditions of Use on this site. If you do not agree to these Terms and Conditions of Use, please do not use this site, app. Please check the Terms and Conditions of Use periodically for changes. Your continued use of this site following the posting of any changes to the Terms and Conditions of Use constitutes acceptance of those changes.
	From time to time, you may be requested to provide That\'s It with personal information. Such personal information is subject to That\'s It Privacy Policy. View the That\'s It Privacy Policy. 
	This site may contain links to third party Web sites (Linked Sites), and may incorporate information obtained from third parties (Third Party Information). The Linked Sites and Third Party Information are not under the control of That\'s It, and That\'s It is not responsible for the contents of any Linked Site or Third Party Information, including without limitation the accuracy, copyright compliance, legality, decency, links or any other aspect of the Linked Sites. That\'s It is not responsible for any form of transmission received from any Linked Site nor is That\'s It responsible if the Linked Site is not working appropriately. That\'s It provides such links and information to you only as a convenience, and the inclusion of any link or Third Party Information does not imply endorsement by That\'s It of the site or any association with its operators. You are responsible for viewing and abiding by the privacy statements and terms of use posted at the Linked Sites. 
	Any dealings with third parties conducted through the site or Linked Sites, including the delivery of and the payment for goods and services, and any other terms, conditions, warranties or representations associated with such dealings, are solely between you and the third party. That\'s It shall not be responsible or liable for any part of any such dealings. 
	In consideration of your use of any services provided on the site, you agree to: (a) provide true, accurate, current and complete information about yourself where prompted by the site (such information being the Personal Data) and (b) maintain and promptly update the Personal Data to keep it true, accurate, current and complete. If you provide any information that is untrue, inaccurate, not current or incomplete, or That\'s It has reasonable grounds to suspect that such information is untrue, inaccurate, not current or incomplete, That\'s It has the right to suspend or terminate any services provided to you by That\'s It and refuse any and all current or future use of That\'s It services (or any portion thereof). 
	You are responsible for all activities undertaken by you using any service provided by That\'s It, including, without limitation, access to materials on the Internet (whether at a password protected site or not) and use of email. All such activities are at your own risk. You shall not use, nor permit others to use, this site or any That\'s It services provided through this site in a manner or for a purpose contrary to these Terms and Conditions of Use. In the event that you access other networks or computing resources, you agree to abide by their respective usage policies. You are responsible for all activities that occur under your password or account, and will keep your password(s) confidential. You will immediately notify us of any unauthorized use of your password or account or any other breach of security. You will not disrupt the functioning of the site, solicit another user\'s password, or otherwise act in a way that interferes with other user\'s use of the site. Nor may you post or distribute any computer program that damages, detrimentally interferes with, surreptitiously intercepts, or expropriates any system, data, or personal information. 
	Services provided by That\'s It are not intended for use by minors. A minor is someone who has not reached the age of majority in the applicable jurisdiction from which the site is being accessed. In the event that you, as a legal guardian, wish to allow a minor to use this site and/or any That\'s It services, you acknowledge that a minor will have permission to access this entire site and any That\'s It services, including without limitation email. You further acknowledge that, as the legal guardian, it is your responsibility to determine whether use of the That\'s It services and/or content transmitted through the That\'s It services is appropriate for a minor. 
	That\'s It does not claim ownership of the materials you provide to That\'s It in any way. However, by posting, uploading, inputting, providing or submitting any such materials, you are granting That\'s It and any necessary sublicenses permission to use your submitted materials in connection with the operation of its business, including, without limitation, the rights to: copy, distribute, transmit, publicly display, publicly perform, reproduce, edit, translate and reformat your submitted material; and to publish your name and any contact information you approve of in connection with your submitted material. No compensation will be paid with respect to the use by That\'s It of your submitted material, as provided herein. That\'s It is under no obligation to post or use any material you may provide and That\'s It may remove any such material at any time in its sole discretion. (By posting, uploading, inputting, providing or submitting your material you warrant and represent that you own or otherwise control all of the rights to your material as described in this section including, without limitation, all the rights necessary for you to provide, post, upload, input or submit the material. Notwithstanding the foregoing, any suggestions, improvements or modifications to That\'s It products and services (Enhancements) made by you or anyone acting on your behalf, including your employees, will be the property of That\'s It without any further consideration to you, whether or not such Enhancements are incorporated into That\'s It products and services. You understand that we are not responsible of nothing, we provide you a service and we do her best to give you the best of it. 
	If you lost information, broke your device or whatever is the issue cause buy That\'s It app. We or not gone give any kind of compensation.  
	Those term and condition can change anytime without no advice. 
	That\'s It app, make no refund ! 
	If you don't understand a traducing of the term and condition.  The english text will be the text That\'s it app gone use for any kind of miss understanding. 
	That\'s It app, or not responsible of the texts, multimedia files,  people exchange with there app. 
	You have to understand, if you use That\'s It app for the purpose of terrorism, fraud, juveniles porno, or other kind of crime, and we have complain about that. We will give your information to authority competent and we can close your account without no advice , no refund. 
	        "
                android:textSize="13sp"
                android:textStyle="bold" />
        </LinearLayout>
    </ScrollView>

    <LinearLayout
        android:id="@+id/terms_lnr_acceptBtns"
        android:layout_width="fill_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_alignParentBottom="true"
        android:orientation="horizontal"
        android:paddingBottom="5dp"
        android:paddingLeft="10dp"
        android:paddingRight="10dp"
        android:weightSum="100" >

        <Button
            android:id="@+id/terms_btn_accept"
            android:layout_width="0dp"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginRight="5dp"
            android:text="Accept"
            android:textAllCaps="false"
            android:textSize="17sp"
            android:textColor="@android:color/white"
            android:background="@drawable/custom_contact_selector"
            android:layout_weight="50"
             />

        <Button
            android:id="@+id/terms_btn_deny"
            android:layout_width="0dp"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_weight="50"
            android:layout_marginLeft="5dp"
            android:text="Decline"
            android:textAllCaps="false"
            android:textSize="17sp"
            android:textColor="@android:color/white"
            android:background="@drawable/custom_groups_selector" />
    </LinearLayout>

</RelativeLayout><!-- From: file:/D:/StudioWorkSpace/That's%20It%20SVN/app/src/main/res/layout/terms_conditions_activity.xml -->